let bridgertonQuestions = [
	{
		question:
			'Complete the quote: "Why settle for a ______, when you can have a prince?"',
		choiceA: 'Lord',
		choiceB: 'Man',
		choiceC: 'Duke',
		choiceD: 'Nigel Berbrooke',
		correctAnswer: 'Duke',
	},
	{
		question: 'Who is the eldest Bridgerton brother?',
		choiceA: 'Anthony',
		choiceB: 'Colin',
		choiceC: 'Benedict',
		choiceD: 'Will',
		correctAnswer: 'Anthony',
	},
	{
		question: 'What was the name of this guy, who was obsessed with cheese?',
		choiceA: 'Lord Nolan',
		choiceB: 'Mr Wetherby',
		choiceC: 'Mr Finch',
		choiceD: 'Lord Birch',
		correctAnswer: 'Mr Finch',
	},
	{
		question: 'How many Bridgerton siblings are there in total?',
		choiceA: '4',
		choiceB: '8',
		choiceC: '7',
		choiceD: '6',
		correctAnswer: '8',
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the name of the Featherington housekeeper?',
		choiceA: 'Mrs Colson',
		choiceB: 'Mrs Varley',
		choiceC: 'Mrs Cliffe',
		choiceD: 'Mrs Goode',
		correctAnswer: 'Mrs Varley',
	},
	{
		question: "How did the Duke's mother die",
		choiceA: 'She fell off a horse',
		choiceB: 'In childbirth',
		choiceC: 'She caught an awful plague',
		choiceD: 'In a duel',
		correctAnswer: 'In childbirth',
	},
	{
		question:
			"You should definitely know this, what is the Duke's boxing pal called?",
		choiceA: 'James',
		choiceB: 'Ben',
		choiceC: 'Thomas',
		choiceD: 'Will',
		correctAnswer: 'Will',
	},
	{
		question: 'How did Anthony and the Duke first meet?',
		choiceA: 'They attended Oxford together',
		choiceB: 'At a ball hosted by Lady Danbury',
		choiceC: 'They were introduced by a mutual friend',
		choiceD: 'They attended a duelling class together',
		correctAnswer: 'They attended Oxford together',
	},
	{
		question: 'What century is Bridgerton set in?',
		choiceA: '17th',
		choiceB: '18th',
		choiceC: '19th',
		choiceD: '20th',
		correctAnswer: '19th',
	},
	{
		question: 'How are the Bridgerton siblings named?',
		choiceA: 'Based on their starsigns',
		choiceB: 'With the same letter as the month they are born',
		choiceC: 'Alphabetically',
		choiceD: 'After the doctor who was there during the birth',
		correctAnswer: 'Alphabetically',
	},
];